Finding aid for the J. Paul Getty Trust Press Releases and Public Outreach Materials, 1954-1959, 1973-2022 (bulk 1983-2022) IA10011
Institutional Records and Archives
- Press releases, subject files, 1974-2002; 2006; Series II.; 7.08 Linear Feet (8 boxes)
  - J. Paul Getty Museum:
    - Exhibition schedules:
      - Schedule of Exhibitions – Spring/Summer 1996, May 8, 1996 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 124)
      - Exhibition Schedule 1996-1997, January 2, 1996 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 125)
      - Schedule of Exhibitions - Winter/Spring 1996, January 2, 1996 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 126)
      - Schedule of Exhibitions – Revised Winter/Spring 1995, January 9, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 127)
      - Schedule of Exhibitions – Winter/Spring 1995, November 2, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 128)
      - Schedule of Exhibitions – Summer/Fall 1994, July 1, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 129)
      - Calendar versions for audio recording: Summer 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 130)
      - Schedule of Exhibitions – Spring/Summer 1994, April 5, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 131)
      - Calendar versions for audio recording: Spring 1994 (two versions) (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 132)
      - Calendar versions for audio recording: Winter 1993/1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 133)
      - Copy of 10/1/93: Schedule of Exhibition – Winter 1993/1994, October 1, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 134)
      - Calendar versions for audio recording: Fall 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 135)
      - Schedule of Exhibitions – Summer/Fall 1993, July 2, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 136)
      - Schedule of Exhibitions – Summer 1993, April 2, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 137)
      - Schedule of Exhibitions – Spring 1993, January 4, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 138)
      - Schedule of Exhibtions – Fall 1992, July 2, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 139)
      - Schedule of Exhibitions – Summer 1992, April 3, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 140)
      - Schedule of Exhibitions – Spring 1992, January 8, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 141)
      - Schedule of Exhibitions – Winter 1991/1992, October 2, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 142)
      - Schedule of Exhibitions – Fall 1991, June 27, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 143)
      - Schedule of Exhibitions - June, July, August 1991, April 1, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 144)
      - Schedule of Exhibitions – Spring 1991, January 9, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 145)
      - Copy of Changing Exhibitions from the Permanent Collection: 1990-1991 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 146)
      - Schedule of Exhibitions – Winter 1990/1991, October 4, 1990 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 147)
      - Schedule of Exhibitions – Fall 1990, June 28, 1990 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 148)
      - Schedule of Exhibitions – June, July, August 1990, April 6, 1990 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 149)
      - Schedule of Exhibitions – March, April, May 1990, January 4, 1990 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 150)
      - Changing Exhibitions from the Permanent Collection: 1989-1990 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 151)
      - Schedule of Exhibitions – December 1989, January, February 1990, October 9, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 152)
      - Schedule of Exhibitions – September, October, November 1989, July 10, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 153)
      - Schedule of Exhibitions – June, July, August 1989, April 7, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 154)
      - Schedule of Exhibitions – March, April, May 1989, January 4, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 155)
      - List of 1989 Exhibitions from the Permanent Collection (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 156)
      - Schedule of Exhibitions: December 1988 – February 1989, October 7, 1988 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 157)
      - Schedule of Exhibitions and Lectures – September, October, November 1988, July 6, 1988 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 158)
      - Schedule of Exhibitions, Lectures, Concerts – June, July, August 1988, April 6, 1988 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 159)
      - Schedule of Exhibitions and Lectures – March, April, May 1998, January 5, 1988 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 160)
      - Changing Exhibitions – December 1987, January, February 1988, October 6, 1987 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 161)
      - Schedule of Exhibitions 1987-1988, August 28, 1987 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 162)
      - Schedule of Exhibitions and Lectures – September, October, November 1987, July 7, 1987 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 163)
      - Schedule of Exhibitions and Lectures – June, July, August 1987, April 7, 1987 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 164)
      - Schedule of Exhibitions and Lectures – March, April, May 1987, January 12, 1987 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 165)
      - Schedule of Exhibitions and Lectures – December 1986 through February 1987, October 23, 1986 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 166)
      - Changing Exhibitions 10/1986 through 2/1988, October 3, 1986 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 167)
      - Schedule of Exhibitions and Lectures – September, October, November 1986, August 8, 1986 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 168)
      - Schedule of Exhibitions and Lectures – June, July, August 1986, May 23, 1986 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 169)
      - Special Exhibition Schedule – November 1982 to January 1984, October 8, 1982; January 7, 1983 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 170)
    - Museum departments:
      - Antiquities:
        - Aphrodite, 1988:
          - Aphrodite Statement and Acquisition Policy, 1988 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 11)
            [Note includes: Release on Statement on the Aphrodite 8/3/88; Release on Museum's Acquisitions Policy and the Aphrodite 9/30/88; Release on Museum's Acquisitions Policy, the Aphrodite, and Other Antiquities 9/30/88]
          - Response to Press Reports on Aphrodite Statue, August 5, 1988 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 12)
          - Acquisition of Greek Aphrodite Statue, July 25, 1988 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 13)
        - Kouros, 1990-1992:
          - Kouros Statue, December 23, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 8)
          - Colloquium on Kouros, May 12, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 9)
          - Comparative Study of Kouros, July 6, 1990 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 10)
        - Fleischman Collection, 1994; 1996:
          - Fleischman Collections of Greek and Roman Antiquities, June 12, 1996 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 1)
          - Ancient Comedies at the Getty, September 20, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 2)
          - Ancient Art from the Collection of Barbara and Lawrence Fleischman, July 27, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 3)
          - A Passion for Antiquities: Fleishman Collection, July 27, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 4)
            [Note: Identical to 4/29/1994 book listing in Trust under "Publications]
          - Caption Sheet for Fleischman Collection: Object Highlights (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 5)
          - Related Events: Fleischman Collection (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 6)
          - Exhibition Fact Sheet: Fleischman Collection (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 7)
        - Alexander the Great 10/22/1996-1/5/1997 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 14)
        - Symposium on Ancient City of Alexandria, March 25, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 16)
        - The Wanderings of Odysseus: Fall Drama, August 14, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 17)
        - Two Exhibitions: L'arte del Vasaio: The Italian Renaissance Potter's Art (Maiolica) / Preserving the Past, January 18, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 18)
        - New Acquisitions of Bronze Sculpture, De Vries and Susini, November 13, 1990 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 19)
        - The Art of Bronze Casting: Dirty Business/Princely Bronzes, January 8, 1990 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 20)
        - Ancient Art of Cyprus Exhibition, January 4, 1990 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 21)
        - Recent Acquisitions of Greek Art, November 4, 1986 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 22)
        - Greek Vase Videodisc, August 1986 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 23)
        - Commemorating Vesuvius' Eruption, August 8, 1984; (includes photo quality print) (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 24)
        - Animals in Ancient Art Exhibit (Canceled): 8/8/1982 to 9/19/1982, 1981-1982; (includes release for Cleveland Museum of Art 10/2/1981) (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 25)
        - Herbert Hunt Collection 6/81, October 26, 1981 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 26)
        - Summaries for Cesears and Citizens and The Herbert Hunt Exhibits, April 26-July 12, 1981 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 27)
        - Egyptian Mummy Portraits of Fayum, March 4, 1981 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 28)
        - Herculaneum Excavations, August 9-September 17, 1976 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 29)
        - Recent Acquisitions of Antiquities, June 1-September 3, 1976 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 30)
        - The Bronze Statue of a Youth, May 7, 1975 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 31)
        - Honore Daumier "Histoire Ancienne" 5/1/1975 to 6/15/1975, April 1975; (includes USC 4/23/1975 release) (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 32)
        - Recent Acquisitions of Ancient Art 12/15/1974 to 2/1/1975, 1974-1975 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 33)
        - Splendors of Ancient Rome, November 20, 1974 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 34)
        - The Making of a Hero: Alexander the Great from Antiquity to the Renaissance, October 10, 1996-January 5, 1997 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
      - Drawings:
        - Hans Holbein Exhibition, November 13, 1982-March 27, 1983:
          - Hans Holbein The Younger: Photo of "Sir Thomas More" drawing with caption (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 43)
          - 65 Hans Holbein Photos of Portraits (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 44)
          - Holbein and the Court of Henry VIII Exhibition Information, 1982 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 45)
            [Note: includes Schedule for Stages of Work to be Completed; Memorandum 1/20/1982 on Plan for Film Program for Holbein Exhibition; List for Sign Locations; Coordinated Programs 9/20/1982; 10-Second Release 9/20/1982; Press Preview Set for 11/12/1982; Press Clip; List of Photographs Sent to Art International]
          - Press Clippings and Advertising for Hans Holbein Exhibit (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 46)
          - More Press clippings and Advertising for Hans Holbein Exhibit (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 47)
          - Hans Holbein Press Kit for Pierpont Morgan Library Exhibit (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 48)
            [Note: Includes Mobil Foundation Pamphlet; Release (no date); Fact Sheet; Public Programs; History of Collection; About The Pierpont Morgan Library]
          - Holbein Press Preview and Luncheon, November 11, 1982 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 49)
            [Note: Includes Sign-in Sheet; Advertisement in Local Newsletter; Event Setup Schedule; Menu]
        - French Master Drawings Exhbit from the Rouen Museum, February 10, 1982-March 20, 1982:
          - Rouen Museum Fact Sheet, February 1, 1982 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 50)
          - French Master Drawings Exhibit, Rouen Museum, December 21, 1981 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 51)
          - Rouen Museum Educational Programs, December 21, 1981 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 52)
          - Press Packet, 1981 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 53)
            [Note includes: International Exhibitions Foundation Release 4/30/1981; National Gallery of Art Release 7/22/1981; Saturday Drawing Workshops]
          - Rouen Museum Press Clippings (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 54)
        - Michelangelo to Gericault: Valton Exhibitions, October 10, 1981-December 20, 1981:
          - Michelangelo to Gericault: Valton Exhibition, September 9, 1981 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 55)
            [Note includes: Exhibition Information Sheet and Press Clipping]
          - Valton Exhibition (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 56)
            [Note includes: 5 Photos of Drawings; Negative of Drawing; Introduction to Exhibit in French]
        - Juanes to Goya: Spanish Drawings, exhibition on view at the Getty Center, September 14-November 28, 1999 (Box 2013.IA.66-01)
        - The Body Beautiful: Artists Draw the Nude (1450-1850), on view at the Getty Center, December 14, 1999-February 27, 2000 (Box 2013.IA.66-01)
        - Italian and Flemish Renaissance Acquisitions, January 28, 1999 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 58)
        - Zuccaro Acquisitions, June 8, 1999 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 57)
        - Figure Drawings, November 18, 1996 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 59)
        - Information Sheet: Compositional Drawing 16th to 19th Centuries 8/31/1996-12/08/1996 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 60)
        - The Human Face in Four Centuries of Drawings 1500-1900, December 26, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 61)
        - Exhibition of Johnathan Richardson Senior's Collection, November 8, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 62)
        - Flemish Drawings of 16th and 17th Centuries Exhibit, August 7, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 63)
        - Drawn Toward Nature: Landscape and Gardens in Ancient-Regime France, May 30, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 64)
        - Drapery and Costume in European Drawings from 15th to 18th Centuries, December 4, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 65)
        - Exhibition to Michelangelo Drawings, December 4, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 66)
        - Draft of 16th and 17th Century Dutch Drawings, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 67)
        - 16th Century Ornamental Designs, April 22, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 68)
        - 18th and 19th Century European Drawings, February 7, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 69)
        - 16th and 17th Century Drawings, December 3, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 70)
        - Power of Myth: European Mythological Drawings of 15th through 19th Centuries, September 10, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 71)
        - North Italian Drawings of 15th through 17th Centuries, June 10, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 72)
        - Getty Drawings at the Metropolitan Museum of Art, April 28, 1993; (includes Exhibition Checklist, Lecture Schedule, and Gallery Talks) (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 73)
        - Tiepolo Drawings from Metropolitan Museum, March 15, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 74)
        - Central European Drawings of 16th and 17th Centuries, December 17, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 75)
        - 16th and 17th Century Italian Drawings, October 22, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 76)
        - Italian Master Drawings, March 31, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 77)
        - European Landscape Drawings 15th through 19th Centuries, August 4, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 78)
        - 17th Century Dutch Drawings, May 22, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 79)
        - 16th Century Northern European Drawings, December 20, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 80)
        - Drawings of the Nude, July 30, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 81)
        - 16th and 17th Century Northern European Drawings, May 10, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 82)
        - Pontormo and Other Florentine Artists, March 11, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 83)
        - 17th and 18th Century French Drawings, November 29, 1990 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 84)
        - 17th and 18th Century Italian Drawings Opening, November 13, 1990 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 85)
        - 17th and 18th Century Italian Drawings, September 13, 1990 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 86)
        - Italian Renaissance Drawings, June 28, 1990 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 87)
        - Dutch and Flemish Drawings on Display, April 17, 1990 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 88)
        - 18th and 19th Century Drawings, January 30, 1990 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 89)
        - Renaissance and Mannerist Drawings In Northern Europe, November 16, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 90)
        - 17th Century Italian Drawings, August 29, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 91)
        - 15th and 16th Century Italian Drawings, June 13, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 92)
        - Final List of German Drawings in Exhibition, May 5, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 93)
        - 18th and 19th Century Drawings on Display, April 7, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 94)
        - German and Swiss Drawings, January 10, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 95)
        - Dutch and Flemish Drawings on View, October 25, 1988 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 96)
        - Italian and French Drawings in Two Exhibitions, May 24, 1988 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 97)
        - Northern European 16th and 17th Century Drawings Exhibition, March 15, 1988 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 98)
        - 18th Century Drawings, December 17, 1987 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 99)
        - Landscape and Mannerist Drawings Exhibition, July 21, 1987 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 100)
        - Three Exhibitions of Old Master Drawings, December 8, 1986 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 101)
        - Masterpieces from the Drawings Collection, September 8, 1986 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 102)
        - Note on the relevence of the Spencer Architectural Drawings, December 6, 1985 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 103)
        - Drawings Added to Permanent Collection, May 9, 1984 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 104)
        - Leonardo da Vinci Anatomical Drawings: 11/15/1980 to 2/15/1981, 1980-1981 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 105)
          [Note includes: Release on 9/19/1980 (1 duplicate copy); Public Information Survey, Spring 1981; Schedule of Talks and Lectures at the Getty]
        - Steiner Collection: Renaissance and Baroque Drawings, April 10, 1978 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 106)
        - Rembrandt Etchings Exhibit 11/15/1977 to 12/17/1977, November 1, 1977 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 107)
        - Goya Etchings Exhibit 6/8/1976 to 8/18/1976, May 26, 1976 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 108)
      - Education:
        - New Information Center, May 2, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 142)
      - Manuscripts:
        - Illuminating the Renaissance, 2003; [3 folders] (Box 2013.IA.66-01)
          Includes Communications public relations campaign summary book
        - French Manuscript Illumination of the Late Middle Ages, on view at the Getty Center, August 3-September 26, 1999 (Box 2013.IA.66-01)
        - Art and Science: Joris Hoefnagel, on view at the Getty Center, Stag Beetle (Albrecht Durer), October 12, 1999-January 1, 2000 (Box 2013.IA.66-01)
        - Ingeborg Psalter Acquisition, July 7, 1999 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 109)
        - Hours of Jeanne d'Evereux (English and Spanish), March 11, 1998 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 110)
        - Stammheim Missal Acquired, March 21, 1997 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 111)
        - Manuscript Illumination of the Thirteenth Century, November 18, 1996 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 112)
        - Giovanni Boccaccio Acquisition (with Information Sheet), August 28, 1996 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 113)
        - Illuminating the Mind's Eye: Memory and Medieval Book Arts (7/23/1996 to 10/1/1996) (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 114)
        - Ten Centuries of French Illumination, March 11, 1996 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 115)
        - The Crucifixion in Medieval and Renaissance Manuscripts, December 26, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 116)
        - Book Arts of Isfahan: Diversity and Identity in Seventeenth-Century Persia, October 24, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 117)
        - Devotion and Desire: Views of Women in the Middle Ages and Renaissance, July 7, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 118)
        - Exhibition of Armenian, Jewish, and Courtly Book Arts of 17th Century Persia, May 22, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 119)
        - Illuminated Choir Books of the Middle Ages and Renaissance, March 17, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 120)
        - Medieval and Renaissance Manuscript Illuminations, November 16, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 121)
        - International Style: Courtly Art around the Year 1400, August 11, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 122)
        - Ars et Ingenium: The Illuminator's Craft and Genius / The Making of a Medieval Book, May 25, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 123)
        - Fouquet's Century: Transformations in French Painting 1415-1530, January 14, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 124)
        - Harmonies of Heaven and Earth: Medieval and Ren. Musiscians and Instruments, November 22, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 125)
        - The Cult of Saints in the Middle Ages and Renaissance, August 30, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 126)
        - Early Medieval and Romanesque Manuscripts, May 28, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 127)
        - The Psalms and Their Illustration, February 23, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 128)
        - Illuminating the Past: Historical Texts of the Middle Ages and Renaissance, December 11, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 129)
        - Art and Science: Joris Hoefnagel and the Representation of Nature in the Renaissance, July 20, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 130)
        - Manuscripts and Americans: An Exhibition in Honor of Franklin D Murphy, May 22, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 131)
        - The Passion of Christ in Medieval and Renaissance Manuscripts (includes List of Related Events), February 26, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 132)
        - Jean Fouquet Manuscripts, February 14, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 133)
        - The Decorated Letter, November 21, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 134)
        - French Manuscript Illumination of the Later Middle Ages, August 20, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 135)
        - Monasteries and Manuscripts, May 16, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 136)
        - The Apocalypse and Other Visions in Medieval Illuminated Manuscripts, February 20, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 137)
        - Manuscripts: One Thousand Years of the Bible, November 16, 1990 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 138)
        - Illuminated Devotional Manuscripts, August 16, 1990 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 139)
        - Illuminated Secular Manuscripts, May 15, 1990 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 140)
        - Visions of Tondal, February 20, 1990 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 141)
          [Note: includes 2/20/1990 Release; Photo Quality Copies of Pages of Works; List of Illustrations; Advance Book Information; Request for Photographic Services]
        - The Art of the Written Word: Calligraphy in Medieval and Renaissance Manuscripts, November 16, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 142)
        - Illuminated German and Central European Manuscripts, August 22, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 143)
        - Acquistions of Illuminated Manuscripts, 1984-1989, May 23, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 144)
        - Vie a mon desir: Illuminated Manuscripts and Their Patrons, February 24, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 145)
        - Copy of Release for Sotheby's: Eight Manuscripts to be Sold on 12/6/1988 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 146)
        - The International Gothic Style, November 22, 1988 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 147)
        - Unilluminated Manuscripts to be Sold, October 13, 1988 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 148)
        - The Leiden "Aratea": Ancient Constellations in Medieval Manuscript, September 13, 1988 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 149)
          [Note: includes Memorandum 7/29/1988 and outline of meeting regarding exhibition]
        - Flemish Manuscripts, May 31, 1988 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 150)
        - Illuminated Italian Manuscripts, February 23, 1988 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 151)
        - Early Medieval and Romanesque Manuscripts, November 24, 1987 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 152)
        - Iluminated French Manuscripts of the Late Middle Ages, August 25, 1987 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 153)
        - The Decorated Letter, May 28, 1987 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 154)
        - Monasteries and Manuscripts, February 26, 1987 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 155)
        - Illuminated Gothic Manuscripts, December 8, 1986 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 156)
        - Illuminated Secular Manuscripts, September 8, 1986 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 157)
        - Illuminated Manuscripts, June 6, 1986 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 158)
        - Manuscripts Added to Permanent Collection, June 4, 1984 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 159)
        - Renaissance Painting in Manuscripts, April 11, 1983 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 160)
      - Paintings:
        - Ercole De Roberti, the Renaissance in Ferrera, on view at the Getty Center, April 27-July 11, 1999 (Box 2013.IA.66-01)